http://www.austwarehouse.com.au/privacy-policy

PRIVACY POLICY
The Fromm Packaging Australia Pty Ltd website is owned and operated by Fromm Packaging Australia Pty Ltd which is referred to as “We”, “Our” and “Us” in this privacy policy.
Collection and Purpose
This privacy policy states how We collect and use both personal information and statistical information and follows the guidelines set by the Australian Privacy Principles and the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth).
We collect your personal information disclosed to us during the subscription process. We may also collect personal information from you in the course of your use of our Site including, but not limited to the online enquiry forms and any comments made on the Site, including but not exclusive to the Site blog. We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, subscribe to the newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personal identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.
In addition, we also collect cookies from your computer, which enables us to tell when you use the Site and also to help customise your website experience.
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilised and other similar information.
The purpose for which we collect personal information is to provide you with the best service experience possible on the Site. Some provision of personal information is optional. However, if you do not provide us with certain types of personal information, you may be unable to enjoy the full functionality of the Site.
Your personal information
Personal Information We hold may include Your name, email address, current and previous address, telephone or mobile phone numbers, trading names and bank account details. We hold Your Personal Information on servers located in Australia.
Anti-spam
Fromm Packaging Australia Pty Ltd is committed to observing and complying with its obligations at all times under the Spam Act 2003 (Cth). By completing an online enquiry form, your contact details will be added to our database and they will be used to contact you for notices of any Fromm Packaging Australia Pty Ltd promotions or newsletters. You may unsubscribe from the database, you will stop receiving any further messages from Fromm Packaging Australia Pty Ltd in the future.
How we use your personal information
Your personal information may be used to verify your identity, provide the product and services you have requested or may require, administer and manage the delivery or creation of products and those services, including charging, billing and collecting debts.
Access and correction
Pursuant to the Australian Privacy Principles from the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth), you are allowed access to, and correct, the personal information we hold about you in certain circumstances. If you would like to obtain such access or withdraw your consent, please contact us on email at info@fromm-pack.com.au or phone 1800 023 890.
Third party websites
Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.
Changes to Privacy Policy
We reserve the right to amend this Policy at any time. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately. If we make a significant change to the Policy, we may issue a notice by email or through notice on the home page of the Site. We encourage you to check the Policy from time to time to check for changes.
Last updated: 1/8/17
Fast Product Finder
We can help you find the right product to meet your needs
Quote Request
Contact us
Quote Request
Please complete the form below and one of our friendly sales agents will be in contact within one business day.
Call now 1800 940 356
Where did you find us today?
Thank you for your enquiry!
We will be in contact within
one business day.
